Finding aid for the John Fahey papers LSC.1862
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 5. UCLA Institutes, 1972-2009
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- CIRID space assignments and correspondence regarding expenses, 1980-1997 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- notes on sample estimates and test form, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- transparencies for lab results (graph images), 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- WHO recommended nomenclature for human leukocyte differentiation antigen, 1984-1997 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- normal ranges and data for CD4+ T- cell counts, 1988-1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- ACTG studies, Immunology ATL Steering Committee sessions, focus group summaries, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Heimlich Investigation -- correspondence regarding accusation letter (Dr. Bob Smith letter), denial of involvement and other issues relating to investigation, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Heimlich Investigation -- correspondence with Dan Willier, Esq., 2003 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Heimlich Investigation -- media relations, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Heimlich Investigation --Information on and articles by Dr. Henry Heimlich, 1994-2003 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Heimlich Investigation -- Chen Xiao Ping correspondence and articles, 1996-2003 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Heimlich Investigation -- correspondence with Najib Aziz, 1999-2003 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Heimlich Investigation -- malariotherapy articles and information, 1984-2003 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Heimlich Investigation -- public information requests, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Heimlich Investigation -- miscellaneous, 2007 June 22 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Letter regarding litigation
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- UCLA International AIDS conference, correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- Symposium on HIV/AIDS, Development of Antiviral Therapies, Palm Springs, 2001 March 8-11 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- grant applications and research travel award information and correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- Center for AIDS Research (CFAR) international activities progress report, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- Center for AIDS Research (CFAR) International Core response to questions for review, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - UCLA Center for AIDS Research (CFAR) renewal application, 2003 July (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - UCLA Center for AIDS Research/AIDS Institute -- International Core program information, supplemental information, correspondence, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - UCLA Center for AIDS Research (CFAR) - International Core correspondence, notes, program information, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - UCLA Center for AIDS Research (CFAR) -- correspondence, notes, program information, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- special international funding, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- international working group/advisory group, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- UCLA International AIDS Advisory Group correspondence, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Interactive Think Tank on International AIDS Research -- research proposals, audio tapes, 2001-2005 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - UCLA AIDS International Workshop, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute Travel Award -- correspondence and recipients, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Fahey Emeritus offer and office space correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Accounts, budgets for programs, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Immuno-Biology Group statement of receipts and expenditures, 1987-2000 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Expenses for travel and meeting, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - UCLA Logon service request, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Fahey letters, certificates of membership to Immunological societies, license to practice, 1987-1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Fahey merit interview for professorial advancement, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Fahey biographical sketch and data, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Fahey, maps and UCLA newsletter, 1972, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Fahey -- licenses, certificates and correspondence related to professorship and advancement, 1979-2000 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Fahey -- personal budget, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Fahey -- Salary information, 1991-2001 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Fahey -- report on outside professional activities, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Fahey - leave of absence, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Fahey - medical staff assignment, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Fahey -- salary information, personal financial statements, confidential correspondence, 1979-2007 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Factor building space, architectural plan, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Fahey -- accreditation correspondence, 1977-1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Fahey - five year review, including letters promoting Fahey from colleagues, 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Fahey -- continuing education certificate, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Fahey -- correspondence regarding immunology program, 1973-1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Saliva studies, correspondence, notes, articles and general information, 1992-1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Saliva studies, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Urine testing kits, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Saliva studies, including correspondence, articles and study information, 1991-1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- correspondence, program proposal, activities, fund requests, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- program information, correspondence, funding sources, information regarding Center for AIDS Research, 2005-2008 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - University-wide AIDS Research Program -- correspondence, Task Force agenda, annual report, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with David Gere for AIDS/Arts Activism, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - AIDS in India program, correspondence and goals, 2005-2007 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- Center for AIDS Research Core summary, committee retreat, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- survey, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Center for AIDS Research (CFAR) Supplemental grant information and correspondence, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- international funding, correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- CFAR Core J, International Activities correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - UCLA AIDS Institute -- Rita Effros research proposal for research in immunological function in aging, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - UCLA Clinical and Translational Science Institute (CTSI) program organization and call for applications, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - UCLA Center for Integrative Medicine correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- 6. International Societies, 1976-2001
  This series contains correspondence, program information, outlines and agendas for International Society meetings, travel documentation, fliers and pamphlets.
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- council correspondence, program information, 1999-2001 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- council correspondence, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- council correspondence, QASI, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- council correspondence, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- Clinical Immunology Committee, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- Clinical Immunology Committee, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- Clinical Immunology Committee, Amsterdam, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- Amsterdam, 1993 April (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Clinical Immunology talk, 1995 March 31 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Talks, Mark Twain, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- Mexico, Alergia e Inmunologia Clinica, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- Mexico, Alergia e Inmunologia Clinica, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- Italy, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- Netherlands, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- Switzerland, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- United Kingdom, key articles, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- Australia, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- training program for various countries, 1995-1997 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- training program for various countries, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- USA, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- members and correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- Education, UCLA Background, 1993-1999 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- handouts, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- meeting and budget, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- resource materials, 1976-1997 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- Recognition training in LA and Europe, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- talks, management, correspondence and articles, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- program information, training information, correspondence, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Clinical Laboratory Immunology - correspondence and development information, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Clinical Immunology Society and Clinical Immunology Committee correspondence and information, 1992-1995 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- member list, meeting agenda, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- International Symposium of Clinical Immunology correspondence, 1994-1998 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- 4th International Symposium on Clinical Immunology, 1995-1997 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Clinical Immunology Society -- International Committee CIS activities, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Clinical Immunology Society -- 5th International Symposium on Clinical Immunology, correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- correspondence, budgets and agenda, 1992-1994 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- lists of members, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- committee report, correspondence, general information, 1992-1994 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- correspondence, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- correspondence and various society information, 1990-1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Clinical Immunology Committee (IUIS) -- meeting report, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- council correspondence, budgets, meeting agendas, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- council correspondence, meeting agendas, budgets, notes, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- program information, correspondence, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- Barcelona, correspondence, budgets, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- Council correspondence, reports, notes, budgets, member lists, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- Council meeting in Mexico, correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- Council correspondence, expenditures, notes, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - International Union of Immunological Societies -- 2nd International Symposium of Clinical Immunology, Budapest, Hungary, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Federation of African Immunological Societies -- 3rd FAIS meeting, Cape Town, South Africa, 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Immunological Societies of Asia-Oceania (FIMSA) -- First FIMSA Congress, correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Asociacion Latinoamericana de Inmunologia (ALAI) -- IV Latin American Congress of Immunology, XII Mexican Congress of Immunology, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Federation of African Immunological Societies -- 3rd African Immunology Congress, Cape Town, South Africa, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - World Health Organization - Immunology course for Nairobi, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- 7. Correspondence, 1968-2009
  This series contains correspondence with colleagues from all over the world, primarily with Indian colleagues.
  - Ahmed, Razzaque, 1986-1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Noel Rose, American Board of Medical Laboratory Immunology, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Afrasiabi, Rahmatollah, 1985-2001 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Afrasiabi, Rahmatollah, 1975-1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Africa Center, UCLA, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - American Academy of HIV Medicine, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - American Association of Immunologists, 1993-1999 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Abbott Laboratories, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Abdel-Kariem, Mohamed Faisal, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Abdel-Kariem, Mohamed Faisal, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Abdel-Kariem, Mohamed Faisal, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Adelstein, Stephen, 1997-1998 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, A, 1990-1999 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Beall, Gil, 1993-2005 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Bach, Jean-Francois, 1988-2000 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Bennet, Tracy, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Arnon, Ruth, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Ashman, Bob, 1986-1994 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Aziz, Najib, 1998-2002 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - B.A. Askonas, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, B, 1993-2000 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Bloom, Eda, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Bonavida, 1988-1999 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Bower, Julie, 1986-2004 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Nguyen, Anh-Tuan, 1992-2010 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Benton Dickison, 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Bermudez, Saul, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Bianco, Nicolas E., 1996-1999 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Brandt, Michael, 2001-2002 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Black, Allen, 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Bentwich, Zvi, 1980-2004 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Britton, Sven, 1984-2008 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Bryson, Yvonne, 1994-2001 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Bubbers, Eric, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Butch, Anthony, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Bramhall, John, 1985-1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Braun, Jonathan, 1984-1999 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Bridbord, Ken, 2000-2006 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Breen, Elizabeth, 1997-2007 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Bradley, John, 1995-2009 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Chem Lab, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Cancer Center UCLA, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Cancer Center UCLA, 1998-1999 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - CDC HIV/AIDS, 1993-1998 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, C, 1993-2001 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Cousins, Norman, 1979-1990 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Clinical and Experimental Immunology, 1990-1999 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Clinical Immunology and Immunopathology, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Clinical and Diagnostic Laboratory Immunology, 1995-1999 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Central European Journal of Immunology, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Council on Health Research for Development (COHRED), 1995-1998 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Cole, Steve, 1995-2006 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Cole, Steve, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Concern Foundation, 1996-1998 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Corby, Nan, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Covington, Chandice, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Clinical Immunology Society, 1998-2002 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Center for Research Excellence, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Center for HIV Identification, Prevention and Treatment Services (CHIPTS), 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Center for Vulnerable Populations Research (CVPR), 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Clinical Immunology Society, 1992-1997 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Chiappeli, Francesco, 1999-2005 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Chopin, Dominique, 1985-1990 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Princess Chulabhorn, Chulabhorn Research International, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Clement, Loran, 1987-1995 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Canilla, Pasquale, 1986-1991 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Center on Aging, UCLA, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Chen, Irwin, 1989-2000 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Cheredeev, Anatoly, 1995-2000 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Bass, Hong, 1992-2004 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Bass, Hong, 1990-1995 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Bass, Hong, 1992-2002 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - DNCB (dinitrochlorobenzene), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Donovan, Suzanne, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Douglas, Steve, 1993-1999 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Dopp, Joel, 1995-2000 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Dopp, Joel, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Detels, Roger, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Detels, Roger, presentations, 2005-2006 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Detels, Roger, 1984-2008 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, D, 1993-2009 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Epitope, Inc., 1994-2000 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - JLF Photo Occasion, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Ellison, George, 1980-2000 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Elhilali, Mustafa, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Effros, Rita, 1986-1999 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Gonzalez-Figueroa, Evelyn, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, E, 1990-2000 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - DRG International, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - FOCIS (Federation of Clinical Immunology Societies), 2005 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Flaskerud, Jacquelyn, 1986-2001 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Franchini, Miriam, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Fryland, Mette, 1999-2002 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Fuchs, Dietmar, 1991-2008 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Fawzy, Fawzy, 1985-1990 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Feldman, Marc, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Fernandez-Cruz, Eduardo, 1994-1997 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Finegold, Ira, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Fan, Jiang, 1991-2008 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Family Health International, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, F, 1984-2000 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Gonzalez-Figueroa, Evelyn, 2005-2006 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Goodman, Howard, 1989-1997 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Gorre, Mercedes, 1998-2000 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - GPA (Global Programme on AIDS), 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Golub, Sidney, 1977-1999 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Giovannoni, Gavin, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Giri, T.K., 1994 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Glick, Gail, 1984-2003 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Giorgi, Janis, 1983-1998 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Gere, David, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Genetic Systems, 1986-1992 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Gallo, Robert, 1983-1993 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Gates Foundation, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Gatti, Richard, 1980-1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Granger, Douglas, 1996-2009 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Gottlieb, AIDS- 25 Years, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Gottlieb, Michael, 1984-2001 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Grimm, Elizabeth, 1980-1985 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, G, 1990-2008 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Hadden, John, 1991-1996 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Haase, Ashley, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Hahn, Bevra, 1979-1997 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Heber, David, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Herzenberg, Leonard, 1990-1993 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Herberman, Ronald, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Hered, Barbara, 1998-2000 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Hofmann, Bo, 1987-2002 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Hofmann, Bo, papers, 1985-1996 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Hofman, Florence, 1980-2000 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - HSPC (Human Subject Protection Committee), 1998-2000 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, H, 1993-2000 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Isacescu, Valentin, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Immunology Training Grant, 2000-2005 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Immune Response Corporation, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - International Visa & Courses, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - International AIDS Society, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - International AIDS Vaccine Initiative, 200-2001 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - International Council of Scientific Unions, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Immune Response Corporation, 1995-1999 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Isacescu, Valentin, 1986-2000 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Ivashchenko, Milana, 1991-1994 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Ivashchenko, Milana, Fogarty, 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Jackson, Anne, 1990-1993 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Juillard, Guy, 1978-1982 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Jury, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, I and J, 1993-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Health Research Policy and Systems, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Kagan, Jon, 1983-2009 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Kanowith-Klein, Susan, 1977-1994 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Kato, Rose, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Kedar, Eli, 1984-1988 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Keys to desk, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Koniak-Griffin, Deborah, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Khaitov, Rakhim, 1984-1997 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Kim, Kyuchan, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Kishimoto, Tadamitsu, 1983-1997 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Kemeny, Margaret, 1985-2005 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Kermani-Arab, Vali, 1981-2004 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, K, 1997-2002 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Liu, Min, 1990-1995 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Liu, Brian, 1987-1991 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Levy, Jay, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Lichtenstein, Alan, 1984-1986 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Ling, Walter, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Krause, Richard, 1977-1997 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Lane, Cliff, 1997-1999 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence, David, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Lewis, Chas, 1976-1988 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, L, 1993-2000 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Mehra, Narinder, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Melmed, Raphael, 1987-2002 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Mercado, Ulises, 1995-1999 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Menon, Palat, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Merrill, Jean, 1977-2009 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Messing, Edward, 1982-1987 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - McChesney, Mike, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Martinez-Maza, Otoniel, 1982-2003 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Mawhinney, Helen, 1981-1987 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - McDonald, Matt, 1998-2009 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Murahata, Richard, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Moody, Dewey, 1982-1988 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Metzger, Henry, 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Mitchell, Anne-Marie, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Mitsuyasu, Ronald, 1989-2001 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Miedema, Frank, 1993-1996 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Jeffery, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Miller, Jim, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Department of Microbiology and Immunology, 1988-2000 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Department of Microbiology and Immunology and Molecular Genetics, 2000-2007 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, M, 1992-2000 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Najera, Evelyn, 1993-2006 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Nyamathi, Adeline, 1999-2003 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Nyamathi, Adeline, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Nyamathi, Adeline, 2006-2008 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Nishanian, Pari, 1983-2001 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Nel, Andre, 1987-2006 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Newman, Peter, 2000-2001 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Nielsen, Karin, 1992-2009 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Nathanson, David, 1968-1978 (Box 49, Folder 4)